We must guarantee France's digital sovereignty.
For instance, we cannot...
You might think it is a secondary example,
but I disagree with Microsoft equipping the French army,
I disagree with Microsoft installing its operating systems on our sensitive equipments
such as missiles, anti-ballistic missiles, submarines and so on, because that's what we are using today.
So if I were elected, all this would be over, we'll use other operating systems.
I am also in favor of internet freedom, and more particularly, I am opposed to online profiling.
The right to access contents should not depend on our financial means or on our preferences.
Our freedom should be total and we should all be able to access the same contents whether we are producers, consumers or users.